Sedrak Adoyan

Frontend developer

Georgia. (relocate is available)

Phone: (+995) (599) 00-73-27

Email: set.adoyan@gmail.com

Telegram: https://t.me/defk1lla

Github: https://github.com/DefK1lla/ **LinkedIn**: www.linkedin.com/in/defk1lla

About

Software development enthusiast with almost 3 years commercial experience on React, NextJS. I have experience in command and own projects developing (including pet and freelance), from simple landing pages to complex crypto marketplaces and online casinos. I am self-supporting, have good self education skills, and love to solve complex and interesting tasks.

Work experience

Junior Gate – Lead Frontend developer

August 2023 - Present

Building websites from landing pages to NFT projects with complicated design.

Skills: FSD architecture, NextJS, Redux, SCSS, Git/GitHub, REST API

Responsibilities: Built various components in ReactJS, integration of services with REST API, code-review, task decomposition

Freelance– HTML Coder/Frontend developer

November 2021 – August 2023

- <u>defk1lla.github.io/conf-propb</u>
- defk1lla.github.io/maran/dist
- defk1lla.github.io/yuzhny

Education

Georgian Technical University-

Bachelor's Degree

September 2018 – June 2022

Faculty: Informatics and control systems

Speciality: Informatics

The Rolling Scopes School

JS-FE-2022Q3

Certificate: app.rs.school/certificate/pm0ltoeh

Final project: aithub.com/d1elit/final-task/pull/22

Pet-projects

Code

https://github.com/DefK1lla/react-port
 folio

Preview

https://defk1lla.vercel.app/

Skills

- Frontend: JavaScript(ES5/ES6), TypeScript, ReactJS, NextJS, Redux/Redux Toolkit, Thunk/Saga, Mobx, AJAX (XHR/axios/fetch)
- Backend: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Strapi, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTTP, REST

- Mobile: React Native, Expo
- HTML/CSS: BEM, Bootstrap, Material UI, Styled Components, Semantic layout, Cross-browser layout, Adaptive layout (Mobile-first/Desktop-first)
- Preprocessors: SASS/SCSS, LESS, Sylus
 HTML template engines: PUG(Jade), EJS
- Instruments: npm, Gulp, Webpack, Git/GitHub
- Graphic editors: Figma, Photoshop, Zeplin
- Other: Docker, AWS, JQuery, Python, Selenium Webdriver, C++
- Languages: Russian(C1), Armenian(C1), Georgian(B1), English(A2)

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)